# Moh (Zoso) Robati

Solutions Architect Software Developer

## Contact

•

(226) 698-3672



moh. robati. shirzad@gmail.com



220, 350 Columbia West St., Waterloo, ON, Canada



linkedin.com/in/moh-robati

#### Education

Sep 2017 - May 2023

# **University of Waterloo**

Master of Applied Science, Computer Software

- Waterloo, ON, Canada

#### **Tehran Polytechnic**

Bachelor of Science, Computer Engineering

- Tehran, Iran

# **Key Skills**

#### **Amazon Web Services**

AWS Solutions Design

#### **MERN Stack**

MongoDB, ExpressJS, ReactJS, NodeJS

#### Rust

low-level programming

#### **React Native**

cross-platform mobile app development

## **Awards**

Fall 2021

International Master's Excellence Award (UWaterloo)

#### Profile

I'm an AWS certified solutions architect with over 4 years of experience as a Full-Stack Javascript developer. MERN stack is my primary choice for development, though I'm willing to compromise on the M and E parts.. I've gained knowledge in almost all the sections of a business software stack. Whether it's infrastructure design, determining the most efficient cloud solution, DevOps and organizational operations, spinning up web servers and implementing business logic in the back-end, front-end development and client-side application design, count me in.

# **Professional Experience**

January 2022 - April 2023

Waterloo, ON, Canada

# **Teaching Assistant** at University of Waterloo

- I served as a teaching assistant for 4 consecutive semesters during my graduate studies at the University of Waterloo:
  - •.1. W23 ECE459: Programming for Performance
  - •.2. F22 ECE252: System Programming and Concurrency
  - •.3. S22 ECE252: System Programming and Concurrency
  - •.4. W22 ECE459: Programming for Performance

May 2022 - July 2022

BC, Canada (Remote)

#### **Javascript Engineer** at Charthouse Lawyers

- Building automation solutions for legal softwares so the users can do routine task pipelines faster. I helped Charthouse Lawyers with:
  - •.1. Requirements elicitation
  - •.2. Specifying the optimal software solution for each requirement.
  - •.3. Designing the access system and the central management scheme.

January 2020 - August 2020

Tehran, Iran

# Front-end Team Leader at Utopia

- Utopia is a start-up based in Tehran and tries to address various problems that Iranian farmers are struggling with. A few of my friends and I got an offer to design and implement a completely robust and error-free software system for this company. I helped Utopia in multiple areas:
  - •.1. Requirements elicitation
  - •.2. Helping with the right project management scheme.
  - •.3. Leading a group of four people in the front-end section.